Austin Baxley

🗣 Atlanta, Georgia, United States 🛎 AusBaxley@gmail.com 🛘 678-435-3558 🛅 in/abaxley2 📤 https://github.com/abaxley2

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with experience in designing, maintaining, and building websites and web applications. Demonstrates leadership in fast-paced goal-oriented environments. Specializes in JavaScript and have experience with using MySQL, NoSQL, Node.js, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars, and React.

PROJECTS

Regex Tutorial

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp · August 2021

- · Developed a working tutorial on Regular Expressions that resulted in an A.
- · Explained in detail each aspect of Regex and it's applicable use.
- · Successfully deployed a GitHub Gist.
- · GitHub Gist: https://gist.github.com/abaxley2/a796040212cdac792dc67c286ba42a41

Get Money Smart

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp · July 2021

- · Created a mobile-responsive banking web application as a tool for teachers.
- · Created and tested API routes.
- · Successfully deployed application to Heroku resulting in an A.
- · Technologies Used: MySQL2, Sequelize, Express.js, Node.js.
- · GitHub Link: https://github.com/mlward639/Get_Money_Smart
- · Deployed Link: https://polar-river-76787.herokuapp.com/

Market Finder

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp · June 2021

- · Created a web application that used third party APIs to locate local farmer's markets by location.
- · Wrote and managed project assignments.
- · Successfully deployed the application through GitHub resulting in an A.
- · Technologies Used: jQuery, TailwindCSS.
- · GitHub Link: https://github.com/abaxley2/Market-Finder
- · Deployed Link: https://abaxley2.github.io/Market-Finder/

EXPERIENCE

Restaurant Manager

Tin Lizzy's Cantina• Launched new product offerings.

January 2020 - May 2021, Kennesaw, GA

- Laurence new product orienings.
- · Managed a large and intricate inventory of product and ordered product to fill any gaps.
- · Managed a large and diverse team and wrote all scheduling.

Band Director

Cobb County Schools

September 2013 - May 2016, Marietta, GA

- $\cdot \, \text{Developed curriculum and conducted clinics to enable students to learn in an adaptable setting.} \\$
- · Performed and organized at over 40 performances including concerts, festivals, and parades.
- \cdot Instructed and maintained a group of over 400 students each year.

Restaurant Manager

CentraArchy Restaurant Management Group

March 2013 - December 2019, Atlanta, GA

- $\cdot \, \text{Sourced}, \text{developed}, \text{and trained new restaurant managers}.$
- $\cdot \ Increased \ key \ metrics \ including \ guest \ counts, \ revenue \ per \ guest.$
- · Increased overall revenue by 15%.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of Music in Music Education

Kennesaw State University · Kennesaw, GA · 2012

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Express, Mongoose, Graphql Apollo, MVC, Mongo Db, NoSQL, MySQL